{
    "subject": "resource/Costanzo_Preve",
    "predicate": "ontology/era",
    "object": "resource/20th-century_philosophy",
    "human_readable": "Costanzo Preve was a philosopher of the 20th century.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9719275832176208,
            "question": "What century was Costanzo Preve a philosopher in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8601300716400146,
            "question": "Was Costanzo Preve known for his work in philosophy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7865575551986694,
            "question": "How did Costanzo Preve's philosophy impact the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.739861011505127,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Costanzo Preve's philosophical ideas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6658914685249329,
            "question": "What are some of the key themes explored in Costanzo Preve's philosophy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5272994637489319,
            "question": "Are there any notable figures who were influenced by Costanzo Preve's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49286797642707825,
            "question": "What were some of the major works written by Costanzo Preve?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49028506875038147,
            "question": "Were there any specific schools of thought that influenced Costanzo Preve?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38893547654151917,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Costanzo Preve's personal life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3054291605949402,
            "question": "Where did Costanzo Preve live and work during his lifetime?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Costanzo Preve was a philosopher of the 20th century.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7764_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Costanzo Preve's personal life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7764_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any specific schools of thought that influenced Costanzo Preve?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7764_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were some of the major works written by Costanzo Preve?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7764_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7764_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7764_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7764_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7764_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7764_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7764_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7764_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7764_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7764_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7764_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information about Costanzo Preve being an Italian philosopher and political theoretician, specifically mentioning that his era is part of 20th-century philosophy. This supports the statement that Costanzo Preve was a philosopher of the 20th century."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}